...to understand what is called the tensegrity phenomenon on
...テンセグリティ現象を理解するために
the developmental plane
発生学的レベルで
and the balance plane of the heart's homeostatic processes in the organization of metabolic fields.
そして、代謝場の組織における心臓の恒常性プロセスのバランスのレベルで。
Dr. M. B. Schmitt, who had the opportunity to conduct real research on
M. B. Schmitt博士は、真の研究を行う機会がありました。
ontogenesis,
個体発生について、
to observe movements, he deduced a kind of concept of
動きを観察し、彼はある種の概念を導き出しました。
metabolic field.
代謝場。
He was the one who started.
彼が始めたのです。
He began to introduce this concept of boundary tissue and interior tissue.
彼は境界組織と内部組織という概念を持ち込み始めました。
Under the microscope, from what he saw, there were two main types of
彼が顕微鏡で見たところ、大きく分けて2種類の
tissues.
組織がありました。
A type of tissue that was at the boundary, that formed
境界にある組織で、
the boundaries in all vesicles and things like that.
すべての小胞などの境界を形成していました。
And a tissue that brought nourishment, an interior tissue, a nutritive tissue.
そして、栄養を運ぶ組織、内部組織、栄養組織。
And the idea is that...
そして、その考えは...
These tissues, you see them,
これらの組織は、あなたが見るように、
ectoderms, endoderms,
外胚葉、内胚葉、
you understand, it corresponds
ご理解いただけたと思いますが、それは対応しています。
to epithelial tissues or
上皮組織または
connective tissues. This is a
結合組織。これは
histological reading.
組織学的解釈です。
This is a classic angiological reading.
これは古典的な血管学的な解釈です。
This is a
これは
biodynamic angiology reading
生体力学的血管学の解釈です。
tubulichemic. A link that I will
化学的チューブ。私がこれからお話しする関連性ですが、
give you like this, that I throw in the air,
このように、私はそれを空中に投げかけますが、
but I won't explain it much.
あまり詳しく説明しません。
Many women, for example,
例えば、多くの女性が、
who have problems with the uterus,
胃の慢性的な問題、
of the chronic gastric type
または食道炎などの問題を抱えています。
or even esophagitis or things like that.
実際、その原因は骨盤にあります。
In fact, the origin of this is in the small pelvis.
分子レベルでは
On a molecular level
濃度の分化を伴い
with a differentiation of concentration
ホルモンについて、
on hormones,
神経ホルモン
neuro-hormones
またはホルモン、
or hormones,
胃型の分子。
gastric-type molecules.
非常に多くの場合、実際には、
Very often, in fact,
筋膜のバランスを再調整する必要があります。
it comes, to release the quality of the
それは、胃の生理機能の質を解放するために来ます。
stomach's physiology.
胃の生理機能の質を解放するために来ます。
This is a collicular link, for example.
これは、例えば、丘の連結です。
Because we're going to start playing with the vascular system,
血管系、つまり内皮系と遊び始めるからです。
which is the link, the endothelial system.
それは連結であり、内皮系です。
It's a huge link in the body.
それは体内の巨大な連結です。
I make a small scratch here, there's blood.
ここに小さな引っかき傷を作ると、血が出ます。
I make a small scratch, there's blood in there.
小さな引っかき傷を作ると、そこに血が出ます。
It's a kind of very deep conductive tissue,
それは非常に深い導電性組織の一種であり、
that must be known how to use in its electrical force.
その電気的な力を利用する方法を知る必要があります。
with the interdependence of organizational planes on symbolics,
象徴的な、象徴的な力に基づいた組織化の計画の相互依存性とともに。
symbolic forces.
象徴的な力。
We can almost symbolize. To symbolize means to gather, to unify the system.
ほとんど象徴化できます。象徴化とは、システムをまとめ、統一することを意味します。
What we mainly retain is that it is a tissue where there is no
私たちが特に覚えているのは、それが鬱血のない組織であるということです。
congestion.
鬱血のない組織であるということです。
Always, in other words, dependent here. Whereas here, there can be phases of congestion.
常に、言い換えれば、ここでは依存しています。一方、ここでは鬱血の段階があるかもしれません。
But at the same time,
しかし同時に、
It is a motor and a resistance for the growth of
それは組織の成長のための原動力であり抵抗でもあります。
boundary tissues.
限界の。
You have a vessel that arrives, it's a motor,
血管が到着すると、それは原動力です。
because it gives strength to the tissue that feeds on it.
なぜなら、それはそこから栄養を得る組織に力を与えるからです。
In that sense, it's a motor,
その意味で、それは原動力です。
since it transports food,
栄養を運ぶので、
and at the same time, it doesn't grow at the same rate.
そして同時に、同じ速度では成長しません。
It is both the motor,
それは同時に原動力であり、
for growth and the brake for growth. It seems paradoxical,
成長のための原動力であり、成長のためのブレーキでもあります。それは逆説的に思えるかもしれませんが、
but it is not paradoxical.
しかし、それは逆説的ではありません。